loveawake.com 2018-04-12

# 

### Privacy Policy

At Loveawake.com we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Loveawake.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

#### What information do we collect?

When you sign up for Loveawake.com services, you provide us with contact. Contact information typically includes your name and e-mail address

While you are a Loveawake.com member, we manage information with regard to your account status, choice of services, and member logs. In addition, we may store members' electronic mail and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications.

We may at times also use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a web site can store in a designated file on your computer. Cookies allow a web application to respond to you as an individual. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the web application can tailor its operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes.

Loveawake.com will not use or disclose your personal information for purposes other than those described in this policy. 

#### How do we use this information?

The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze web traffic and to improve the content of our web site. Cookies may be used to facilitate your customer interaction with us. For example, we may use a cookie on the landing page of products sold online which record the customer information that is required on the order form and then forward this information to our internal sales tracking database.

Loveawake.com may also use third-party companies to provide various services (including but not limited to instant messaging and advertising) when you use this website. If you use those services, the internet protocol address (IP address) of the computer you are using to access the website may be disclosed to those third-party companies, and we may use attributes (including but not limited to age and gender) that you provide in your public profile to display relevant ads to you. Loveawake.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of these third-party companies or any other external websites linked to this site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these other websites when you leave our website.

By issuing this website you acknowledge that

(a) we cannot ensure the security or privacy of information you provide through the Internet and your email messages, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the use of such information by other parties; 

(b) we are not responsible for, and cannot control, the use by others of any information which you provide to them and you should use caution in selecting the personal information you provide to others through the Service; and

(c) we cannot assume any responsibility for the content of messages sent by other users of the Service, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the contents of any communications you may receive from other users. We cannot guarantee, and assume no responsibility for verifying, the accuracy of the information provided by other users of the Service.

You may not use the Service for any unlawful purpose. If you use this service unlawfully we will pass along all information to law enforcement. We may refuse to grant you an ID or nickname that impersonates someone else, is protected by trade-mark or proprietary law, or is vulgar or otherwise offensive, as determined by us in our sole discretion.

We do not share any personal information with third parties, and we do not send advertising to our members.

Members may opt out of receiving newsletters and/or notices from Loveawake.com by sending a request to office@loveawake.com or by clicking the opt out links you can find in every letter our members receive.
